Guide to the Steinway & Sons Oral History
Steinway & Sons Oral History
Oral History of American Music
Steinway & Sons Oral History
1978 1981
OHIV
Oral History of American Music
266 Computer Files
General
126 interviews as of September 9, 2021. This finding aid describes digitized copies of the interview recordings in this collection. Oral History of American Music also holds the original recordings, on a variety of legacy audio and video formats.
Scope and Contents
The Steinway & Sons Oral History traces the history of Steinway & Sons, one of the preeminent manufacturers of pianos, from its years as a family business until its acquisition by CBS in 1972. One-hundred twenty interviews provide a multi-level look at a major musical institution that has made a significant impact on musical culture in the United States and abroad. Interviewees include Steinway family members, piano technicians, factory workers, Steinway agents, and concert pianists.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. The finding aid includes links to stream most interviews online via Oral History of American Music's (OHAM) AV access system, Aviary. Yale users can login to Aviary using their Yale University ID, to stream these interviews without restriction. Other users are able to request access to interviews directly through Aviary. For access instructions, and to request transcripts of an interview, see OHAM's website. This finding aid also includes links to Table of Contents for most interviews.
Some interviews may be restricted. Access to these restricted interviews may only be granted to a patron who has first obtained direct permission from the interviewee or their estate.
Some interviews may not have been digitized or are otherwise not available to stream online. However, these interviews may have been transcribed. Please see contact OHAM for more details.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by surname of interviewee.
Pianos; Piano makers United States; Steinway & Sons
- Allen, Rodgie
  - Allen, Rodgie, 1978 November 21; OHIV 748 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 84 mins; Transcript Page Count: 42 pages
    Interview Location
    London
    Conditions Governing Access
    This material is restricted. Access may be granted to a patron who has obtained direct permission from the interviewee or their estate.
    Allen, Rodgie
- Arrau, Claudio
  - Arrau, Claudio, 1979 December 7; OHIV 810 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Transcript Page Count: 17 pages
    Douglaston, NY
    Arrau, Claudio, 1903-1991
- Balsam, Arthur
  - Balsam, Arthur, 1978 September 13; OHIV 733 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 25 mins; Transcript Page Count: 14 pages
    New York, NY
    Balsam, Arthur, 1906-1994
- Bamman, Henry
  - Bamman, Henry, 1978 August 23; OHIV 719 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 64 mins; Transcript Page Count: 38 pages
    Bamman, Henry A.
- Barber, Anthony
  - Barber, Anthony, 1978 August 30; OHIV 721 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 71 mins; Transcript Page Count: 37 pages
    Tuxedo Park, NY
    Barber, Anthony, 1920-2005
- Berman, Lazar
  - Berman, Lazar, 1978 November 3; OHIV 744 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 39 mins; Transcript Page Count: 18 pages
    Berman, Lazar, 1930-2005
- Bernuth, Shirley
  - Bernuth, Shirley, 1979 January 18; OHIV 770 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 101 mins; Transcript Page Count: 33 pages
    Bernuth, Shirley
- Bogyos, John
  - Bogyos, John, 1978 May 23; OHIV 704 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 108 mins; Transcript Page Count: 65 pages
    North Floral Park, NY
    Bogyos, John
- Borell, Stephen
  - Borell, Stephen, 1979 January 29; OHIV 774 a-d; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 147 mins; Transcript Page Count: 72 pages
    Borell, Stephen
- Brendel, Alfred
  - Brendel, Alfred, 1980 January 18; OHIV 814 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 57 mins; Transcript Page Count: 21 pages
    Brendel, Alfred, 1931-
- Bruhn, Gretel
  - Bruhn, Gretel, 1979 March 23; OHIV 779 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 52 mins; Transcript Page Count: 20 pages
    Hamburg, Germany
    Bruhn, Gretel
- Bruhn, Gretel and Elizabeth Peterson
  - Bruhn, Gretel and Elizabeth Peterson, 1979 March 22; OHIV 777 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 85 mins; Transcript Page Count: 39 pages
    Bruhn, Gretel; Peterson, Elizabeth
- Casadesus, Gaby
  - Casadesus, Gaby, 1980 January 4; OHIV 812 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 61 mins; Transcipt Page Count: 32 pages
    Casadesus, Gaby
- Chapin, Betty Steinway
  - Chapin, Betty Steinway, 1978 September 12; OHIV 731 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 80 mins; Transcript Page Count: 53 pages
    Chapin, Betty Steinway
- Chapin, Schuyler
  - Chapin, Schuyler, 1979 August 1; OHIV 802 a-c; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 118 mins; Transcript Page Count: 16 pages
    Chapin, Schuyler, 1923-2009
- Chapin, Theodore Steinway
  - Chapin, Theodore Steinway, 1979 January 23; OHIV 772 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 34 mins; Transcript Page Count: 42 pages
    Chapin, Theodore Steinway
- Chasins, Abram
  - Chasins, Abram, 1978 December 27; OHIV 795 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 81 mins; Transcript Page Count: 17 pages
    Chasins, Abram, 1903-1987
- Cliburn, Van
  - Cliburn, Van, 1980 October 2; OHIV 818 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Transcript Page Count: 23 pages
    Cliburn, Van, 1934-2013
- Cochrane, Lydia Steinway
  - Cochrane, Lydia Steinway, 1978 October 18; OHIV 734 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Transcript Page Count: 51 pages
    Chicago, IL
    Cochrane, Lydia Steinway
- Comstock, Peter
  - Comstock, Peter, 1978 August 29; OHIV 720 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 22 mins; Transcript Page Count: 12 pages
    Ivorytown, CT
    Comstock, Peter
- Cushing, Howard
  - Cushing, Howard, 1978 October 18; OHIV 735 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 68 mins; Transcript Page Count: 36 pages
    Cushing, Howard
- Danforth, Mrs. Francis J.
  - Danforth, Mrs. Francis J., 1978 September 27; OHIV 726 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 27 mins; Transcript Page Count: 15 pages
    Danforth, Leonie Alexandre
- Dichter, Misha
  - Dichter, Misha, 1979 June 1; OHIV 798 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 44 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Dichter, Misha, 1945-
- Dorfman, Ania
  - Dorfman, Ania, 1978 December 27; OHIV 767 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 63 mins; Transcript Page Count: 35 pages
    Dorfman, Ania
- Drasche, Fred
  - Drasche, Fred, 1978 June 6; OHIV 706 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 67 mins; Transcript Page Count: 59 pages
    Ormond Beach, FL
    Drasche, Fred
- Ducksch, Robert and Gerhard Andacht
  - Ducksch, Robert and Gerhard Andacht, 1979 March 24; OHIV 778 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 19 mins
    Berlin, Germany
    Andacht, Gerhard; Ducksch, Robert
- Durham, R. Gregory
  - Durham, R. Gregory, 1979 May 8; OHIV 793 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 86 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Durham, R. Gregory
- Esteban, Julio
  - Esteban, Julio, 1980 March 23; OHIV 820 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 41 mins
    Baltimore, MD
    Esteban, Julio
- Fiocco, Anthony
  - Fiocco, Anthony, 1979 May 8; OHIV 788 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 19 mins; Transcript Page Count: 11 pages
    Fiocco, Anthony
- Firkunsny, Rudolf
  - Firkunsny, Rudolf, 1978 November 2; OHIV 742 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Transcript Page Count: 34 pages
    Firkunsny, Rudolf
- Firstenberg, Harry
  - Firstenberg, Harry, 1978 October 30; OHIV 758 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 52 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Yonkers, NY
    Firstenberg, Harry
- Fitzgerald, Winston
  - Fitzgerald, Winston, 1979 September 6; OHIV 809 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 61 mins; Transcript Page Count: 28 pages
    Fitzgerald, Winston
- Frank, Claude
  - Frank, Claude, 1978 December 7; OHIV 762 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 74 mins; Transcript Page Count: 44 pages
    Frank, Claude, 1925-2014
- Furlong, John
  - Furlong, John, 1978 May 25; OHIV 705 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 64 mins; Transcript Page Count: 45 pages
    Long Island City, NY
    Furlong, John
- Gigax, Richard
  - Gigax, Richard, 1979 May 3; OHIV 790 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 64 mins; Transcript Page Count: 30 pages
    Gigax, Richard
- Glazebrook, Michael
  - Glazebrook, Michael, 1978 November 22; OHIV 750 a-c; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 150 mins; Transcript Page Count: 52 pages
    Glazebrook, Michael
- Glazebrook, Robert
  - Glazebrook, Robert, 1978 November 21; OHIV 749 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 79 mins; Transcript Page Count: 39 pages
    Glazebrook, Robert
- Glazer, Frank
  - Glazer, Frank, 1978 December 15; OHIV 765 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 36 mins; Transcript Page Count: 45 pages
    Glazer, Frank
- Gould, Morton
  - Gould, Morton, 1979 April 3; OHIV 783 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 47 mins; Transcript Page Count: 22 pages
    Gould, Morton, 1913-1996
- Graffman, Gary & Naomi & Roger Clemens
  - Graffman, Gary & Naomi & Roger Clemens, 1978 November 13; OHIV 747 a-d; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 156 mins; Transcript Page Count: 70 pages
    Graffman, Gary, 1928-; Clemens, Roger; Clemens, Naomi
- Hamlin, Barbara
  - Hamlin, Barbara, 1978 September 4; OHIV 729 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 79 mins; Transcript Page Count: 42 pages
    Litchfield, CT
    Hamlin, Barbara
- Hanlet, Alexandre
  - Hanlet, Alexandre, 1979 September 11; OHIV 806 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 29 mins; Transcript Page Count: 13 pages
    Paris, France
    Hanlet, Alexandre
- Hart, Walter
  - Hart, Walter, 1978 May 17; OHIV 702 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 45 mins; Transcript Page Count: 28 pages
    Hart, Walter, 1926-
- Henderson, Skitch
  - Henderson, Skitch, 1978 September 22; OHIV 732 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 41 mins; Transcript Page Count: 27 pages
    Henderson, Skitch, 1918-2005
- Hollander, Lorin
  - Hollander, Lorin, 1979 July 17; OHIV 804 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 52 mins; Transcript Page Count: 27 pages
    Hollander, Lorin, 1944-
- Hupfer, William
  - Hupfer, William, 1978 May 18; OHIV 703 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 76 mins; Transcript Page Count: 49 pages
    Bronx, NY
    Hupfer, William
- Ijams, Mrs. J. Horton
  - Ijams, Mrs. J. Horton, 1978 October 24; OHIV 739 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 60 mins; Transcript Page Count: 41 pages
    Ijams, J. Horton, Mrs.
- Johannesen, Grant
  - Johannesen, Grant, 1979 June 1; OHIV 799 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 44 mins; Transcript Page Count: 13 pages
    Johannesen, Grant, 1921-2005
- Jordan, Alice
  - Jordan, Alice, 1979 January 21; OHIV 773 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 67 mins; Transcript Page Count: 38 pages
    Jordan, Alice
- Keene, Constance
  - Keene, Constance, 1978 December 27; OHIV 801 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 54 mins; Transcript Page Count: 22 pages
    Keene, Constance
- Kehr, Ernest A.
  - Kehr, Ernest A., 1978 July 26; OHIV 712 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 51 mins; Transcript Page Count: 23 pages
    Richmond Hills, NY
    Kehr, Ernest A. (Ernest Anthony), 1911-1986
- Kittredge, Marjorie (Mrs. Charles)
  - Kittredge, Marjorie (Mrs. Charles), 1978 November 28; OHIV 759 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 93 mins; Transcript Page Count: 41 pages
    Boxford, MA
    Kittredge, Marjorie V., 1924-2010
- Kraus, Lili
  - Kraus, Lili, 1979 June 25; OHIV 803 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 41 mins; Transcript Page Count: 16 pages
    Mayflower, NYC
    Kraus, Lili, 1903-1986
- Lateiner, Jacob
  - Lateiner, Jacob, 1978 November 10 1978 November 11; OHIV 764 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 38 mins; Transcript Page Count: 20 pages
    Date note
    There is a date discrepancy between the date noted on the transcript for this interview which is November 10, 1978, and the date noted in OHAM's previous database containing details for each interview in the collection, which dates this interview as November 11, 1978.
    Lateiner, Jacob, 1928-2010
  - Lateiner, Jacob, 1978 December 14; OHIV 764 b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 31 mins; Transcript Page Count: 16 pages
    Date Note
    There is a date discrepancy between the date noted on the transcript for this interview which is November 10, 1978, and the date noted in OHAM's previous database containing details for each interview in the collection, which dates this interview as December 14, 1978.
- Lee, Noel
  - Lee, Noel, 1979 September 14; OHIV 808 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 43 mins; Transcript Page Count: 18 pages
    Interviewer
    Vivian Perlis
    Lee, Noël, 1924-
- Lewenthal, Raymond
  - Lewenthal, Raymond, 1978 October 20; OHIV 737 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 45 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Lewenthal, Raymond, 1926-1988
- Lipkin, Seymour
  - Lipkin, Seymour, 1978 September 22; OHIV 730 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 42 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Lipkin, Seymour
- List, Eugene
  - List, Eugene, 1978 November 10; OHIV 746 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Transcript Page Count: 42 pages
    List, Eugene, 1918-1985
- Little, Ray
  - Little, Ray, 1978 November 24; OHIV 756 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 30 mins; Transcript Page Count: 16 pages
- Livingstone, Robert
  - Livingstone, Robert, 1978 July 26; OHIV 713 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 65 mins; Transcript Page Count: 31 pages
    Livingstone, Robert
- Lodge, Eleanor Ziegler (Mrs. Henry Sears)
  - Lodge, Eleanor Ziegler (Mrs. Henry Sears), 1978 November 28; OHIV 760 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 40 mins; Transcript Page Count: 22 pages
    Beverly, KA
    Lodge, Eleanor Ziegler (Elenita)
- Lympany, Moura
  - Lympany, Moura, 1978 November 23; OHIV 755 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 38 mins; Transcript Page Count: 19 pages
    Lympany, Moura, 1916-2005
- Majewski, Roman de
  - Majewski, Roman de, 1978 September 13; OHIV 723 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 121 mins; Transcript Page Count: 70 pages
    Warwick, NY
    Majewski, Roman de
- Masselos, William
  - Masselos, William, 1978 November 3; OHIV 743 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 81 mins; Transcript Page Count: 38 pages
    Masselos, William, 1920-1992
- Menuhin, Jeremy
  - Menuhin, Jeremy, 1978 November 25; OHIV 757 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 43 mins; Transcript Page Count: 22 pages
    Menuhin, Jeremy
- Mills, Henry
  - Mills, Henry, 1978 September 27; OHIV 727 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 16 mins; Transcript Page Count: 11 pages
    Long Island city, NY
    Mills, Henry
- Moeseley, Carlos
  - Moeseley, Carlos, 1978 November 13; OHIV 794 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 26 mins; Transcript Page Count: 14 pages
    Moeseley, Carlos
- Mohr, Franz
  - Mohr, Franz, 1979 January 16; OHIV 769 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 58 mins; Transcript Page Count: 43 pages
    Mohr, Franz, 1927-
- Mueller, Erich
  - Mueller, Erich, 1978 June 9; OHIV 710 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 75 mins
    Pompano Beach, FL
    Mueller von Asow, E. H. (Erich Hermann), 1892-1964
- Murphy, Paul E., Sr.
  - Murphy, Paul E., Sr., 1978 November 29; OHIV 761 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 68 mins; Transcript Page Count: 19 pages
    Boston, MA
    Murphy, Paul E., Sr.
- Newton, Ivor
  - Newton, Ivor, 1978 November 23; OHIV 754 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 40 mins
    Newton, Ivor
- Ohlsson, Garrick
  - Ohlsson, Garrick, 1978 October 26; OHIV 740 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 70 mins; Transcript Page Count: 56 pages
    Ohlsson, Garrick
- Orcutt, Edwin B. & Cookie (Rosabelle)
  - Orcutt, Edwin B. & Cookie (Rosabelle), 1978 June 9; OHIV 707 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 109 mins; Transcript Page Count: 49 pages
    Orcutt, Cookie (Rosabelle); Orcutt, Edwin B.
- Pace, Robert
  - Pace, Robert, 1978 September 19; OHIV 725 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 57 mins; Transcript Page Count: 34 pages
    Pace, Robert, 1949-
- Paige, H. Ray
  - Paige, H. Ray, 1978 December 7; OHIV 763 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 74 mins; Transcript Page Count: 37 pages
    Darien, CT
    Paige, H. Ray
- Paley, William
  - Paley, William, 1979 June 26; OHIV 800 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 16 mins; Transcript Page Count: 9 pages
    Paley, William S. (William Samuel), 1901-1990
- Peckerman, Edward R.
  - Peckerman, Edward R., 1979 January 22; OHIV 771 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 133 mins; Transcript Page Count: 36 pages
    Washington Depot, CT
    Peckerman, Edward R.
- Perahia, Murray
  - Perahia, Murray, 1980 February 21; OHIV 816 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 40 mins; Transcript Page Count: 21 pages
    Perahia, Murray, 1947-
- Pirola, Joe
  - Pirola, Joe, 1978 May 17; OHIV 701 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 42 mins; Transcript Page Count: 28 pages
    Pirola, Joe
- Pompa, Anthony
  - Pompa, Anthony, 1979 May 8; OHIV 789 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 57 mins; Transcript Page Count: 31 pages
    Pompa, Anthony
- Pramberger, Joseph and Anton
  - Pramberger, Joseph and Anton, 1978 August 10; OHIV 718 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 85 mins; Transcript Page Count: 57 pages
    Albertson, Long Island, NY
    Pramberger, Anton; Pramberger, Joseph
- Reisenberg, Nadia
  - Reisenberg, Nadia, 1979 January 4; OHIV 797 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 37 mins; Transcript Page Count: 17 pages
    Reisenberg, Nadia, 1904-1983
- Rosen, Charles
  - Rosen, Charles, 1979 January 11; OHIV 796 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 43 mins; Transcript Page Count: 23 pages
    Rosen, Charles, 1927-2012
- Ross, John
  - Ross, John, 1978 November 22; OHIV 752 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 23 mins; Transcript Page Count: 13 pages
    Ross, John
- Rubin, David
  - Rubin, David, 1979 May 16; OHIV 813 a-c; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 86 mins; Transcript Page Count: 66 pages
    Rubin, David
- Rubinstein, Arthur
  - Rubinstein, Arthur, 1979 September 13; OHIV 807 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 57 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Rubinstein, Artur, 1887-1982
- Rush, Clarence
  - Rush, Clarence, 1978 September 3; OHIV 728 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 81 mins; Transcript Page Count: 34 pages
    Hartford, CT
    Rush, Clarence
- Sandor, Gyorgy
  - Sandor, Gyorgy, 1979 January 24; OHIV 775 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 105 mins; Transcript Page Count: 28 pages
    Ann Arbor, MI
    Sándor, György, 1912-2005
- Schang, Fred
  - Schang, Fred, 1978 October 24; OHIV 738 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 70 mins; Transcript Page Count: 28 pages
    Schang, Fred
- Schein, Harvey
  - Schein, Harvey, 1979 April 6; OHIV 786 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 38 mins; Transcript Page Count: 19 pages
    Schein, Harvey
- Schmitt, Robert P.
  - Schmitt, Robert P., 1978 October 21; OHIV 736 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 102 mins; Transcript Page Count: 57 pages
    Minneapolis, MN
    Schmitt, Robert P.
- Sehringer, Charles
  - Sehringer, Charles, 1979 March 30; OHIV 780 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 91 mins; Transcript Page Count: 41 pages
    Sehringer, Charles
- Serkin, Peter
  - Serkin, Peter, 1980 February 26; OHIV 815 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 24 mins; Transcript Page Count: 14 pages
    New Haven, CT
    Serkin, Peter, 1947-
- Serkin, Rudolph
  - Serkin, Rudolph, 1980 October 6; OHIV 819 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Transcript Page Count: 20 pages
    Brattleboro, VT
    Serkin, Rudolph
- Shelley, Warner
  - Shelley, Warner, 1978 August 4; OHIV 717 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 62 mins; Transcript Page Count: 25 pages
    Philadelphia, PA
    Shelley, Warner
- Simon, Abbey
  - Simon, Abbey, 1979 October 5; OHIV 805 a; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 44 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Simon, Abbey
- Smith, J. Ascher
  - Smith, J. Ascher, 1978 August 3; OHIV 716 a; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 36 mins; Transcript Page Count: 15 pages
    Smith, J. Ascher
- Squibb, Lionel
  - Squibb, Lionel, 1978 November 23; OHIV 753 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 72 mins; Transcript Page Count: 33 pages
    Squibb, Lionel
- Steinway, Charles
  - Steinway, Charles, 1978 June 16; OHIV 711 a-c; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 107 mins; Transcript Page Count: 66 pages
    Indianapolis, IN
    Steinway, Charles H.
- Steinway, Frederick (Fritz)
  - Steinway, Frederick (Fritz), 1979 April 8; OHIV 784 a-d; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 168 mins; Transcript Page Count: 101 pages
    Amherst, MA
    Steinway, Frederick (Fritz)
  - Steinway, Frederick (Fritz), 1979 April 9; OHIV 784 e-h; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 148 mins; Transcript Page Count: 103 pages
- Steinway, Henry Engelhard (Harry)
  - Steinway, Henry Engelhard (Harry), 1979 March 13; OHIV 782 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 68 mins; Transcript Page Count: 27 pages
    Steinway, Henry Engelhard (Harry)
- Steinway, Henry Ziegler
  - Steinway, Henry Ziegler, 1978 December 21; OHIV 766 a-c; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 125 mins; Transcript Page Count: 77 pages
    Steinway, Henry Ziegler
  - Steinway, Henry Ziegler, 1979 January 19; OHIV 766 d-f; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 125 mins; Transcript Page Count: 77 pages
- Steinway, John Howland
  - Steinway, John Howland, 1978 November 7; OHIV 745 a-e; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 209 mins; Transcript Page Count: 113 pages
    Steinway, John Howland
  - Steinway, John Howland, 1978 December 5; OHIV 745 f-k; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 226 mins; Transcript Page Count: 127 pages
- Steinway, Polly
  - Steinway, Polly, 1979 December 14; OHIV 811 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Transcript Page Count: 41 pages
    Steinway, Polly
- Steinway, Ruth Davis
  - Steinway, Ruth Davis, 1978 July 31; OHIV 715 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 102 mins; Transcript Page Count: 68 pages
    Plymouth, MA
    Steinway, Ruth Davis
- Steinway, Virginia
  - Steinway, Virginia, 1978 September 9; OHIV 722 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 57 mins; Transcript Page Count: 39 pages
    Bantam, CT
    Steinway, Virginia
- Steinway, William
  - Steinway, William, 1979 March 13; OHIV 781 a-b; Harkins, Elizabeth R.; Approximate Running Time: 49 mins; Transcript Page Count: 22 pages
    Steinway, William
- Streep, F.D. (Bud) Jr.
  Streep, F.D. (Bud), Jr.
  - Streep, F.D. (Bud) Jr., 1979 May 3; OHIV 791 a; Approximate Running Time: 40 mins; Transcript Page Count: 19 pages
    Elizabeth R. Harkins
- Taylor, Billy
  - Taylor, Billy, 1981 February 6; OHIV 821 a; Perlis, Vivian; Transcript Page Count: 10 pages
    Riverdale, NY
    Taylor, Billy, 1921-2012
- Tetzlaff, Gustav C.